The camera's on, the smile is bright
Another take in the burning light
They painted the set with a perfect blue But it
doesn't feel real, it doesn't feel true We're
living under a plastic sky They tell me jump, I
ask how high It's just a set, it's all a lie Living
under a plastic sky
Woah
My guitar is clean, the drums are thin.
They polished away all the grit and sin.
I wanna scream, I wanna roar But they just ask me
to sing some more We're living under a plastic
sky They tell me jump, I ask how high It's just a
set, it's all a lie Living under a plastic sky
Is this the dream we were chasing? A different
part, a different face. I'm losing me, I'm
losing you.
You know I love Chastity.
We're living under a plastic sky They tell me
jump, I ask how high It's just a set, it's all a lie
Living under a plastic sky Plastic sky
Feeling so
loose ♪